var names = ["Player 1", "Player 2", "Player 3", "Player 4", "Player 5", "Player 6", "Player 7", "Player 8"];
var questionList = [
{question:"Top 8 Most Common English Letters",wrong:"U",correct:["E","T","A","I","N","O","S","R"]},{question:"Leap Years",wrong:"1900",correct:["2004","2016","1484","1876","2000","2400","1992","852"]},{question:"2015 movies",wrong:"Zootopia",correct:["Inside Out","Minions","Avengers: Age of Ultron","Star Wars: The Force Awakens","Jurassic World","Paddington","Paul Blart: Mall Cop 2","The Martian"]},{question:"Movies sponsored by the Department of Defense",wrong:"X-Men: Days of Future Past (2014)",correct:["The Karate Kid Part II (1986)","Godzilla (1998)","King Kong (2005)","Transformers (2007)","The Silence of the Lambs (1991)","Indiana Jones and the Last Crusade (1989)","Top Gun (1986)","Iron Man (2008)"]},{question:"Top 10 Highest Nominal GDP Countries(According to IMF 2022)",wrong:"South Korea",correct:["Brazil","Italy","Canada","France","India","United Kingdom","Germany","Japan"]},{question:"Ivy Leagues",wrong:"Northwestern",correct:["UPenn","Princeton","Columbia","Yale","Brown","Harvard","Dartmouth","Cornell"]},{question:"Girl's Generation Members",wrong:"Sohee",correct:["Taeyeon","Sunny","Tiffany","Hyoyeon","Yuri","Sooyoung","Yoona","Seohyun"]},{question:"Romance languages",wrong:"German",correct:["Spanish","Portuguese","French","Italian","Romanian","Catalan","Sicilian","Ligurian"]},{question:"Kit Kat Flavors",wrong:"Takoyaki",correct:["Hot Chili Pepper","Edamame Milkshake","Sakura Sake","Maple","Ice Cream","Fruity Cereal","Wasabi","Pumpkin Pie"]},{question:"Invertebrates",wrong:"Snake",correct:["Sea Urchin","Fly","Crawfish","Centipede","Sea Star","Scallop","Spider","Snail"]},{question:"Books in the Old Testament",wrong:"The Gospel of John",correct:["Esther","Daniel","Exodus","Leviticus","Numbers","Deuteronomy","Song of Solomon","Job"]},{question:"Jupiter Moons",wrong:"Phobos",correct:["Europa","Ganymede","Io","Callisto","Thebe","Adrastea","Metis","Amalthea"]},{question:"Andy Warhol Artworks",wrong:"Rose Ring",correct:["Shot Diptych","Campbell's Soup Cans","Banana","Gun","Green Coca-Cola Bottles","Eight Elvis","Silver Car Crash","Cow Wallpaper"]},{question:"Elements on the Periodic Table",wrong:"Delirium",correct:["Osmium","Tanalum","Rutherfordium","Nihonium","Americium","Californium","Einsteinium","Fermium"]},{question:"Minecraft Biomes",wrong:"Eroded End",correct:["Sunflower Plains","Beach","Meadow","Lukewarm Ocean","Snowy Slopes","Windswept Savanna","Sparse Jungle","Birch Forest"]},{question:"La Croix Flavors",wrong:"Lily Durazno",correct:["Coffea Exotica","Beach Plum","Cubana","Guava São Paulo","Pastèque","LimonCello","Múre Pepino","Pomme Bayá"]},{question:"Renaissance Paintings",wrong:"Song of the Shepherd",correct:["Vitruvian Man","Pietà","Holy Trinity","Delivery of the Keys","Virgin of the Rocks","Lady with an Ermine","The School of Athens","Venus of Urbino"]},{question:"The Noble Eightfold Path",wrong:"Right Faithfulness",correct:["Right Understanding","Right Thought","Right Speech","Right Action","Right Livelihood","Right Effort","Right Mindfulness","Right Concentration"]},{question:"Japanese Inventions",wrong:"MP3 player",correct:["Emoji","Jet Ski","Laptop","Selfie Stick","Agar","CRISPR","Fortune cookie","Instant noodle"]},{question:"Words spelled correctly",wrong:"Liquify",correct:["Dilate","Pharaoh","Unnecessary","Narcissistic","Manoeuvre","Bureaucracy","Pronunciation","Entrepreneur"]},{question:"States Who Voted Red in the 2020 Election",wrong:"Georgia",correct:["Texas","Florida","Virginia","Utah","Idaho","Iowa","West Virginia","Alabama"]},{question:"Rice Cakes",wrong:"Num Poh Peay",correct:["Dango","Lontong","Idli","Tangyuan","Puto","Bánh bò","Num Plae Ai","Tteok"]},{question:"Reproductive Parts",wrong:"Amathern Gland",correct:["Fallopian Tubes","Endometrium","Epididymis","Vans Deferens","Seminal Vesicles","Frimbriae","Cervix","Glans"]},{question: "Name a Canadaian province",wrong: "Huron-Wendat",correct: ["Prince Edward Island", "Nova Scotia", "Saskatchewan", "Newfoundland and Labrador", "New Brunswick", "Manitoba"],},{question: "Name someone born before 1900",wrong: "Lyndon B. Johnson",correct: ["Albert Einstein", "Harry S. Truman", "Winston Churchill", "Thomas Edison", "Helen Keller", "Colonel Sanders"],},{question: "Name an Austin Powers character",wrong: "Mike Oxsmall",correct: ["Number 2", "Scott Evil", "Fook Mi", "Robin Swallows", "Fat Bastard", "General Borschevsky"],},{question: "Name an ultimate ability from League of Legends",wrong: "Shadow Flare",correct: ["Unbreakable Will", "Voice of Light", "Glacial Fissure", "Hextech Ultimatum", "Last Caress", "Cataclysm"],},{question: "Name a video game released for the Nintendo Wii",wrong: "LSD: Dream Emulator",correct: ["Call of Duty: Black Ops", "Wii Chess", "Enjoy your Massage!", "Anubis 2", "Alvin and the Chipmunks", "Dragonball Z Budokai Tenkaichi 3"],},{question: "Name a United States involvement with regime change",wrong: "Madagascar",correct: ["South Korea", "Iran", "Indonesia", "Nicaragua", "Laos", "Brazil"],},{question: "Name a former president of the Philippines",wrong: "Yingluck Shinawatra",correct: ["Emilio Aguinaldo", "Manuel L. Quezon", "Jose P. Laurel", "Sergio Osmeña", "Manuel Roxas", "Ramon Magsaysay"],},{question: "Name a Taylor Swift Song",wrong: "Besties",correct: ["Better Than Revenge", "Ivy", "Change", "Betty", "Starlight", "Long Story Short"],},{question: "Name a dog breed",wrong: "Moroccan Griffon",correct: ["Basset Hound", "Australian Shepherd", "Maltipoo", "Chow Chow", "Afghan Hound", "Portuguese Water Dog"],},{question: "Name one of the Apostles in the New Testament",wrong: "Joseph",correct: ["Bartholomew", "James", "Philip", "Matthew", "Andrew", "Simon"],},{question: "Name a word invented by Shakespeare",wrong: "Weary",correct: ["Skim-milk", "Swagger", "Unaware", "Undress", "Critic", "Lonely"],},{question: "Name an anime",wrong: "Watashi no Oshiri ga Ookii!",correct: ["Gintama", "Clannad", "Owarimonogatari", "Monster", "Sen to Chihiro no Kamikakushi", "Berserk"],},{question: "Name a romanized line from Gangnam Style",wrong: "allanggamolla wae hwakkeunhaeya haneungeonji",correct: ["naneun mwol jom aneun nom", "jeongsukhae boijiman nol ttaen noneun yeoja", "ttaega doemyeon wanjeon michyeobeorineun sanai", "ttwineun nom geu wie naneun nom", "kopi hanjanui yeoyureul aneun pumgyeok inneun yeoja", "areumdawo sarangseureowo"],},{question: "Name a character from The Office",wrong: "Paul Keaton",correct: ["Holly Flax", "David Wallace", "Darryl Philbin", "Jan Levinson", "Karen Filippelli", "Hidetoshi Hasagawa"],},{question: "Name an AP course or exam offered by CollegeBoard",wrong: "AP Veterinary Science",correct: ["AP Art History", "AP Comparative Government and Politics", "AP Music Theory", "AP Latin", "AP Physics C: Mechanics", "Studio Art: 3-D Design"],},{question: "Name a territory that gained independence from the United Kingdom",wrong: "Ethiopia",correct: ["Myanmar", "Fiji", "Zanzibar", "Malaya", "Iraq", "Egypt"],},{question: "Asian Americans",wrong: "Mark Lee",correct: ["Elaine Chao", "Zach King", "Roger H. Chen", "Perry Chen", "Ellen Pao", "Ken Jeong"]}];